U.S. Manpower Administration "Manpower Daily Reporter" Newsletters 5380
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- January, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday January 10, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday January 9, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday January 6, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday January 5, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday January 4, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday January 3, 1967. Item is in English.
- February, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday February 28, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday February 27, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday February 24, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday February 23, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday February 21, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday February 20, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday February 17, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday February 16, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday February 15, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday February 14, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday February 13, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday February 10, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday February 9, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday February 8, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday February 7, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday February 6, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday February 3, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday February 2, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday February 1, 1967. Item is in English.
- March, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday March 31, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday March 30, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday March 29, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday March 28, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday March 27, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday March 24, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday March 23, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday March 22, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday March 21, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday March 20, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday March 17, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday March 16, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday March 15, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday March 14, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday March 13, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday March 10, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday March 9, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday March 8, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday March 7, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday March 6, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday March 3, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday March 2, 1967. Item is in English.
- April, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday April 28, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday April 27, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday April 26, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday April 25, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday April 24, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday April 21, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday April 20, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday April 19, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday April 18, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday April 17, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday April 14, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday April 13, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday April 12, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday April 11, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday April 10, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday April 7, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday April 6, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday April 5, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday April 4, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday April 3, 1967. Item is in English.
- May, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday May 31, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday May 29, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday May 26, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday May 25, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday May 24, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday May 23, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday May 22, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday May 19, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday May 18, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday May 17, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday May 16, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday May 15, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday May 12, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday May 11, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday May 10, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday May 9, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday May 8, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday May 5, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday May 4, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday May 3, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday May 2, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday May 1, 1967. Item is in English.
- June, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday June 30, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday June 29, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday June 28, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday June 27, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday June 23, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday June 22, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday June 21, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday June 20, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday June 19, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday June 16, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday June 15, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday June 14, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday June 13, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday June 12, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday June 9, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday June 8, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday June 7, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday June 6, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday June 5, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday June 2, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday June 1, 1967. Item is in English.
- July, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday July 31, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday July 28, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday July 27, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday July 26, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday July 25, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday July 24, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday July 21, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday July 20, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday July 19, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday July 18, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday July 17, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday July 14, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday July 13, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday July 12, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday July 11, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday July 10, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday July 7, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday July 6, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday July 5, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday July 3, 1967. Item is in English.
- August, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday August 31, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday August 29, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday August 28, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday August 25, 1967. Item is in English.